<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>programme on useR! 2018</title>
    <link>https://user2018.r-project.org/categories/programme/</link>
    <description>Recent content in programme on useR! 2018</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://user2018.r-project.org/categories/programme/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Conference wifi</title>
      <link>https://user2018.r-project.org/blog/2018/07/10/wifi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://user2018.r-project.org/blog/2018/07/10/wifi/</guid>
      <description>DataCamp is sponsoring higher speed wifi for the conference. Look for the DataCamp wifi and enter &amp;ldquo;freetrial&amp;rdquo; as the password to get connected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last minute details</title>
      <link>https://user2018.r-project.org/blog/2018/06/29/lastminute/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://user2018.r-project.org/blog/2018/06/29/lastminute/</guid>
      <description>Travel details:  South Brisbane is the closest train station to the convention centre. Airtran is offering a airport train discount, details are on the web site. There are numerous ATMs where you can get Australian dollars. There are NO ATM fees for major banks, NAB, ANZ, Commonwealth, Westpac. It is also possible to exchange money throughhttps://transferwise.com/us/blog/currency-exchange-brisbane. Details on Australian power outlets is on https://www.power-plugs-sockets.com/australia/ You should not bring food into Australia, because customs is very strict on this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updates and news</title>
      <link>https://user2018.r-project.org/blog/2018/05/17/updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://user2018.r-project.org/blog/2018/05/17/updates/</guid>
      <description>FREE Introductory R tutorial, Wed AM: RCurious will run free of charge for whoever is interested, and wants to upskill some before the conference fun starts. Following this there will be a newbies lunch, where you can match up with a conference buddy, if you would like. You still need to sign up for the tutorial, on the Programme menu there is a link to the sign up page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial preference</title>
      <link>https://user2018.r-project.org/blog/2018/03/26/tute-preference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://user2018.r-project.org/blog/2018/03/26/tute-preference/</guid>
      <description>When you register, choose and pay for the tutorial sessions that you would like to participate in. The enter your specific preferences for each session here. We will do what we can to ensure that you get your first choice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tentative programme</title>
      <link>https://user2018.r-project.org/blog/2018/03/23/programme/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://user2018.r-project.org/blog/2018/03/23/programme/</guid>
      <description>An outline of the scientific programme can now be found on the Programme tab. Titles for keynote talks will be completed as we get them. Based on the frequency of accepted abstract keywords, the parallel sessions will be organised (roughly) into six main themes, applications, models, algorithms, visualisation, community/education, bioinformatics. Thursday&amp;rsquo;s dinner programme will feature a short talk by John Mertic of the R Consortium about the funding available for open source projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deadlines extended</title>
      <link>https://user2018.r-project.org/blog/2018/02/25/new-deadlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://user2018.r-project.org/blog/2018/02/25/new-deadlines/</guid>
      <description>There have been a lot of deadlines in the last three weeks for the organisers. We are running a bit slow on reviewing abstract submissions and scholarship applications for useR! We need to push back the deadlines for early registration to March 30, 2018; and also can take abstract submissions until Mar 15.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scholarship applications</title>
      <link>https://user2018.r-project.org/blog/2018/01/25/scholarships/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://user2018.r-project.org/blog/2018/01/25/scholarships/</guid>
      <description>Scholarship applications are now closed.
Do you need some financial help getting to useR! 2018? If so, apply for a scholarship. We have funding to provide a few scholarships already, and still hoping for getting more funding to award more. In addition R Ladies Melbourne are offering two $500 travel scholarships! Decisions on scholarships will be based on potential positive impact on the community of the applicant&amp;rsquo;s participation, encouraging diversity to balance participant demographics for a supportive environment, economic need, and available funds for scholarships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abstract submission</title>
      <link>https://user2018.r-project.org/blog/2018/01/18/abstracts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://user2018.r-project.org/blog/2018/01/18/abstracts/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to present a talk, poster or lightning talk at useR! 2018? You can submit an abstract here. Deadline for abstract submission is Mar 2.
Abstracts will be reviewed on a rolling basis, with three acceptance rounds, approx first week of Feb, third week of Feb, and first week of Mar (before early registration deadline). If there are sufficient quality submissions on a topic a session will be formed early, and authors notified.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial proposals</title>
      <link>https://user2018.r-project.org/blog/2017/11/20/tutorials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://user2018.r-project.org/blog/2017/11/20/tutorials/</guid>
      <description>Want to give a tutorial at useR! 2018? You can submit a proposal at https://goo.gl/forms/RR4UgCnMrgIiLJDk1.
Tutorials are typically half day. We are planning on being able to cover reasonable travel costs of tutorial presenters. The deadline for submitting a proposal is Jan 15, 2018. Notification of proposal success will be early Feb.
The examples of past tutorials are outlined in useR! 2017 Tutorials, which we’d like to see again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keynote speakers</title>
      <link>https://user2018.r-project.org/blog/2017/11/12/keynotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://user2018.r-project.org/blog/2017/11/12/keynotes/</guid>
      <description>We are pleased to announce that the keynote speakers for useR! 2018 are Jenny Bryan, Steph de Silva, Heike Hofmann, Thomas Lin Pedersen, Roger Peng and Bill Venables.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
